Guide to the Stanford University Poster Collection SC1030
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Posters
  - Stanford Presidential Lectures and Symposia in the Humanities and Arts. Pina Bausch, Past Dependencies, Charles Rosen, Svetlana Alpers, Bei Dao. October--November 1999, 2003-036; 8.5 x 25 inches (Box D1)
  - Stanford Presidential Lectures and Symposia in the Humanities and Arts.October-November 1998. Henry Louis Gates, Jr.; Stephen Jay could; Karl Heins Bohrer; Wole Soyinka, Un-dated; 420; 7x20.5 inches (Box map case)
    (in B1)
  - Stanford Quad, 1900; 514-1; 13 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Stanford Quad, 1900; 2015-032; 13.5 x 21.5 inches (Box C11)
  - Stanford Quad, 1902-; 514-3; 14 x 21 inches (Box C7)
  - Stanford Quad, 1911; 514-5; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Stanford Quad, 1969; 514-8; 12 x 18 inches (Box B3)
  - Stanford Red Barn Festival, 2002 Aug 24; 2003-012; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Stanford Red Barn Festival, 2001 Aug 18; 2003-028; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Stanford Repertory Theater, 1967-1968; 5121; 24 x 34 inches (Box not specified)
  - Stanford Sailing Association, Un-dated; 530-23; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
    Organizations, Special- General
  - Stanford Songs [probably a cover for a song book], 1903-; 524-12; 9 x 7 inches (Box A3)
  - Stanford Songs - On Sale Friday [contains same image as in 524-12 but with added text], 1903-; 524-13; 12 x 15.5 inches (Box B2)
  - Stanford Spectacular Stanford Centennial, 1991; 907-02; 22x19.25 inches (Box map case)
    this one signed by some of the performers and mounted on foamcore
  - Stanford Speech Association, 1968; 521-6; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
  - Stanford Stadium, 1928; 5; 23 x 17 inches (Box map case)
  - Stanford Students for Estelle Freedman, 30103; 905-82; 22 x 24 inches (Box D2)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra, 1969; 524-31; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra, 1961 Jun 2; 524-22; 14 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra. Berlioz, Fantastic Symphony, Nov. 22, 1992; 524-57; 17 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Stanford Taiko presents our 17th Annual Spring Concert: "Beneath The Wall", 39935; 2009-002; 10 1/2 x 16 1/2 inches (Box C6)
  - Stanford Union Cafe, Un-dated; 27; 11 x 14 inches (Box A1)
  - Stanford University [2001 calendar]. Visual Arts Services, 2003-033; 13 x 18.5 inches (Box B1)
    Includes illustrations from 1930 Quad
  - Stanford University Calendar 1984-85, 2006-040; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Stanford University Calendar 1985-86, 2006-041; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Stanford University Centennial Year Opening Week September 30-October 7, 1990, 90701; 16x20 inches (Box C10)
  - Stanford University Department of Music presents The Ballad of Baby Doe. Music by Douglas moore, Libretto by John Latouche. West Coast Premiere. May 24, 25, 30, 31, June 1 [1957], 524-20; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Stanford University Department of Speech & Drama presents Moliere: The Learned Ladies and: Feydeau: Don't go Walking Around Naked. Jan./February [1969], 524-30; 17 x 11 inches (Box B2)
  - Stanford University Inn, 1902-; 2; 22 x 14 inches (Box C1)
  - Stanford University is in the Spotlight, 2011; 2011-009; 22 x 28 inches (Box C5)
    U.S. Department of Energy Office of Scientific and Technical Information .EDUconnections
  - Stanford University Jasper Ridge Biological Experiment Area. ENTRANCE BY PERMIT ONLY. Qualified investigators apply to Department of Biological Sciences Stanford University. Trespassers will be prosecuted to the full extent of the law., 2009-022; 10 x 12.5 inches (Box A3)
  - Stanford University Libraries and Academic Information Resouces People. [compilation of group and individual portraits of SUL staff prepared as part of Annual Report], 2006-; 2006-004; 17x22 inches (Box C4)
  - Stanford University Men's Glee Club with the Red Vest Band presents This Night for Song Directed by Robert Mackinnon. Saturday May 23 [1964], 524-23; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Stanford University Men's Glee Club, Robert MacKinnon, Director. Try-outs Fall Quarter [1968], 524-27; 17 x 11 inches (Box B2)
  - Stanford University Photos by Joan Kibbey Taylor, 1988; 905-87 (Box mc 341)
  - Stanford University vs. University of Oregon, 1915; 521-3; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Stanford University. Martin Luther King, Jr. Birthday Commemoration January, 1988 (schedule of events), 909-01; 17 x 11 inches (Box B3)
    Martin Luther King, Jr. Birthday Commemoration
  - Stanford v California (freshmen) 1899, 801-09 (Box C3)
  - Stanford Vietnam Day Teach-in 12:00 Mon, May 17 [1965] to 4:00 AM Tues. White Plaza Mem Aud Major Speakers & Entertainment, 1965 May 17-18; 526-02; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - Stanford vs. the World. The Great Event of the San Jose Rose Carnival. Friday, May 8, Un-dated; 803-25; 7 x 20 inches (Box B1)
    damaged copy
    Athletics -- Track and Field
  - Stanford Wind Ensemble, Arthur Barnes, director with the participation of the Studio Jazz Band, Saturday February 28 [no year], 1970s; 2003-010; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Stanford's Department of French and Italian and Program in Modern Thought and Literature are proud to present: Maryse Conde "Images de l'Afrique de Segou a l'Histoire de la femme cannibale" Monday, June 4, 2007, 2007-014; 11x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Stanford's Martin Luther Kin, Jr. Celebration Committee presents: Pulitzer Prize Winning Playwright August Wilson January 10-17, 1999, 2002-009; 11 x 17 inches (Box B1)
  - Stanford's National Collegiate Champions (tennis), ca, 1978; 805-16; 20x16 inches (Box C8)
  - Stanley Kunitz, 1969; 367; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - Stanord Engineering Association. We Deliver. "The Stanford Engineering Association makes grants to individuals and groups who have idease that will: .....", 1970s; 2003-009; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Start the New Year Right by Subsciring for the Chaparral. Gnuts! A College Romance in Seven Whiffs., circa 1910; 514-10; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
    surface of poster has been scored by a knife
  - State, The: Which People's Friend? A Marxist Analysis with Professor James O'Connor, 1969; 120; 22 x 14 inches (Box C1)
  - Statewide Mecha Conference, November 14 and 15, 1986, Stanford University, 419 (Box C11)
  - STEP Symposium. Satellite test of the Equivalence Principle. April 6-8, 1993 Pisa, Italy. (Stanford University was one of the sponsoring institutions), 905-85; 31 x 20 inches (Box not specified)
  - Stereopticon Lecture: "7000 Years Ago, or The Mysteries of Ancient Egypt.", 1897; 301; 9x12 inches (Box A2)
  - "Stop Thief!", Un-dated; 5043; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Story that Transformed the World, The, 1898; 102; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Strawberry Brunch, 1969; 905-29; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Strawberry Shortcake, 1969; 530-12; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Stu-Fac Vietnam Coffee Hour, Un-dated; 530-28; 18 x 24 in (Box C7)
  - Student Artists-- Art Fair, Un-dated; 522-5; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
    Art Exhibits, Student
  - Student Artists-- Stanford Prize contest, 1967; 522-3; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Student Artists--Student Art Show, 1965; 522-1; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Student Artists- Stanford Art Club, Un-dated; 522-4; 19x24 inches (Box C8)
  - Student Demonstrations- A Community Meeting on Stanford-SRI, 1969; 527-1; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Demonstrations- Act for our Demands- Boycott, 1969; 527-5; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Demonstrations- All-Campus Meeting, 1969; 527-7; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Demonstrations- Boycott, 1969; 527-6; 11 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Demonstrations- Join us at AEL, 1969; 527-2; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Demonstrations- No More Disruption, 1969; 527-4; 11 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Demonstrations- No to the Sit-in is Death to the Issues, 1969; 527-3; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Musical Groups- Concert, 1900; 524-8; 11 x 14 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Musical Groups-"Said Pasha", 1896; 524-3; 11x14 (Box A2)
  - Student Musical Groups-Concert, 1896; 524-4; 9x12 (Box A2)
  - Student Political and Social Involvement- Celebrate Diversity, May 1982, 526-07; 17.5 x 22.5 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Political and Social Involvement- Days of Concern, 1968; 526-5; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Political and Social Involvement- Monster Rally, Un-dated; 526-1; 22 x 28 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Political and Social Involvement- Proposition 187 Will it save our State? a panel discussion, 1994; 526-07; 11 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Political and Social Involvement- Science in Society, 1969; 526-6; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Political and Social Involvement- Stanford Vietnam Day Teach-In, 1965; 526-2; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Political and Social Involvement- Teach-In, 1965; 526-3; 12 x 18 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Political and Social Involvement- The United States in the World Today: Bicentennial Perspectives (series of lectures), circa 1976; 526-08; 17.5 x 22.5 inches (Box C7)
  - Student Political and Social Involvement- Vietnam Summer, 1967; 526-4; 12 x 18 inches (Box not specified)
  - Student Political and Social Involvement-Proposition 187 Will it save our state? a panel discussion, 1994; 526-7; 11x17 (Box map case)
  - Students Artists--Sidewalk Art Show, 1966; 522-2; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Students for a Democratic Society- "The Battle of Algiers", 1969; 525-3; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Students for a Democratic Society- "The Battle of Algiers", 1969; 525-3; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Students for a Democratic Society- "The University's Role in the Community", 1965; 525-1; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Students for a Democratic Society- Where Are the Radicals At?, 1968; 525-2; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Students for a Democratic Society. "The University's Role in the Community." Wednesday April 7 [1965]. Tresidder, 525-01; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
    Student Activities -- SDS
  - Success in Life, 1911; 109; 14 x 11 inches (Box A6)
  - Summer '66, 1966; 905-36; 11 x 14 inches (Box not specified)
  - Summer Season, Un-dated; 511-45; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Super Bowl XIX (January 20, 1985), 1984; 91001; 36 x 24 inches (Box not specified)
  - Swimming Club Dance, Un-dated; 5196; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - SWOPSI [course list] Fall 1984-85, 2006-032; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] [Winter 1979], 2006-029; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
    Date calculated from SC431 listing.
  - SWOPSI [course list] [Winter 1980], 2006-030; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] [1979 or 1980], 2006-028; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] [Autumn 1979 or Winter 1980], 2006-020; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] Fall 1981-82, 1982; 2006-023; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] Fall 1982, 2006-019; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] Spring 1981-82, 1982; 2006-024; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] Spring 1982-83, 1983; 2006-017; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] Spring 1983-84, 1984; 2006-018; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] Spring 1984-85, 1985; 2006-027; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] Winter [Winter 1981], 2006-026; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] Winter 1981-82, 1982; 2006-022; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] Winter 1982-83, 1983; 2006-016; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] Winter 1983-84, 1984; 2006-025; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course list] Winter 1984-85, 1985; 2006-021; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI [course offerings], Fall 1978; 2006-011; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI Education in Action [course list], 1979 Spring; 2006-031; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI presents "The Next 50 Years: The Boest or the Last?" A Symposium on Appropriate Science, Land Use, and Community Development. [1978], 2006-036; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI presents Harlan County U.S.A. Friday October 7 [1977], 2006-035; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI Presents Northern Lights. Cannes Film Fesitval-1979-Best First Feature. April 7 [1979?], 2006-014; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI Presents On Guard. A Red Heart Pictures Production. October 3 [1979?], 2006-015; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI Presents The Peace People of Northern Ireland: The Struggle Against Terroism. Ira Sandperl. Monday January 31, 1977, 2006-012; 8.5 x 14 inches (Box B2)
  - SWOPSI Presents The War at Home. 1980 Academy Award Nominee Best Feature Documentary. Wednesday Oct. 1 [1980?], 2006-013; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Symphony Club Concert in the Chapel Monday Evening, May 2 [1904 or 1910]. Haydn's Sixth Symphony, 524-34; 11 x 14 inches (Box A3)
  - T. J. Cobden--Sanderson: The Master Craftsman, 1969; 20112; 11 x 18 inches (Box B1)
  - "Take the Road Less Traveled", undated; 2015-023; 11.5 x 19 inches (Box B4)
  - Talk to Men, A, 1912; 111; 7 x 10 inches (Box A1)
  - "Taming of the Shrew", 1946; 513-24; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - "Tea for Three", Un-dated; 513-61; 14 x 20 inches (Box C7)
  - Teach- ins. Stanford Vietnam Day. Official Program. [mimeographed sheet of day's events stapled to poster], May 17, 1965; 526-03; 12 x 18 inches (Box C4)
  - The 5th Annual Red Barn Festival, 34566; 905-78; 16 x 22 inches (Box C10)
  - The Agora: Civic Center of Ancient Athens, 1968; 343; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - "The Alchemist", Un-dated; 511-51; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - The American Image Abroad, 1969; 381; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - The Archive of Recorded Sound presents Founder's Day program., Un-dated; 20113; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - The Asian American Theater Project Presents F.O.B. by David Henry Hwang May 14, 15, 16, 1998, 2002-011; 11 x 17 inches (Box B1)
  - The Asian American Theater Project proudly presents 12-1-A. April 24-27th, [2003-] Old Union [includes cast list and photos], 2006-061; 18 x 24 inches (Box C4)
  - The Associates of Stanford University Libraries Inaugural 1981 Stanford Antiquarian Book Fair. September 26-27 Roble Women's Gym., 2007-011; 12.5 x 19 inches (Box C4)
  - The Associates of Stanford University Libraries Second Antiquarian Stanford Book Fair Roble Women's Gym. Friday, September 9th-Sunday September 11th, 1983; 2007-010; 12 x 18 inches (Box B2)
  - The Associates of Stanford University Libraries Third Antiquarian Stanford Book Fair. Friday, Saturday, Nov. 1-2, 1985; 2007-009; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - The Athlete's Body in history, on the field, in society; an interdisciplinary conference ... May 1995, 21101; 16 x 26 inches (Box D2)
  - "The Bacchae", Un-dated; 511-54; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - "The Beggar's Opera", Un-dated; 5126; 11 x 20 inches (Box not specified)
  - "The Bernard Shaw Story", Un-dated; 903-11; 14 x 22 inches (Box C10)
  - The Big Idea: Festival for Automotive Interfaces, 2013 Mar 11; 2014-048; 10.75 x 17 inches (Box A6)
    Automobiles -- Design and construction.; mediaX at Stanford University; Center for Automotive Research at Stanford (CARS); The Revs Program at Stanford; Stanford University. Communication between Humans and Interactive Media (CHIMe) Lab.
  - "The Blue Bird", 1952; 511-37; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - "The Boyfriend", 1967; 5084; 13 x 20 inches (Box C6)
  - The Buddhist Society, 1968; 905-58; 5 x 7 inches (Box not specified)
  - The Buddhist Society, 1968; 905-59; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - The BUDDHIST society meets every Thursday at 7:30 pm, 740 Stanford Ave., Menlo Park.... [1968 penciled on notice, which is handwritten], 905-58; 8 x 5.5 inches (Box A3)
  - The Cardinal Rule! Daily coverage of the Rose Bowl. The Chronicle [S. F. Chronicle newrack card. Dec. 1999], 2003-026; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - "The Cavern", 1967; 5122; 14 x 19 in (Box not specified)
  - The Center for Russian, East European and Eurasian Studies presents Independent Ukraine. The Annual CREEES lecture series on contemporary Ukraine., 2004; 2005-003; 11x17 inches (Box B2)
  - The Chaparral appears Wednesday, September 5, enlarged and much improved., 1902-; 514-2; 14 x 21 inches (Box B1)
  - The Chaparral. $1.00 the Year. 25c the Issue. On the Quad and at All Bookstores., circa 1900; 514-9; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - "The Chimes of Normandy", Un-dated; 513-49; 13 x 17 inches (Box B3)
  - The Coalition for an Academic Community, 1969; 905-69; 11 x 17 inches (Box B3)
  - The Committee for an Open University, 1969; 905-62; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - The Company, 1969; 530-11; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - The Company presents "Burning Bright" by John Steinbeck. Directed by Tony Kelly. Sterling Quad Performance Center., Feb. 9-11, 1984; 513-73; Not listed (Box 341 map case)
  - The Contemporary Industrial Revolution in Eastern Europe, 1967; 336; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - The Cultural Revolution in China and its Consequences, 1969; 369; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A2)
  - The Dangerous Intersection of Race, Gender, and Violence: A Symposium with Andrea Smith & Incite! Women of Color Against Violence Brought to you by the Stanford program in Feminist Studies Thursday April 28, 2007, 2007-015; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - The Democratic Experience in Peru: 1963-68, 1969; 370; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - "The Devil's Disciple", Un-dated; 5044; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - "The Dover Road", Un-dated; 513-66; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - The Dream in Architecture and Landscape. Spring Lecture Series 98 (Apr. 14 to May 26), 1998; 203-14; 12.5 x 9 inches (Box B1)
  - "The Duchess of Malfi", Un-dated; 903-13; 14 x 22 inches (Box C10)
  - "The Dwarfs" and "The Kazoo Man", 1965; 5051; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - The Electoral Wake, 1968; 905-48; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - The Electoral Wake, 1968; 905-51; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - The English Club of Stanford University, Un-dated; 5073; 9 x 12 inches (Box A3)
  - "The English Club Year Book", Un-dated; 514-15; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - "The Ethics of Food and The Environment", January 29 and Febuary 19, 2009; 2009-004; 18 x 12 inches (Box C6)
  - The Existence, Consciousness, and the Social Character of the Victorian Womanly Woman, 1969; 372; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A2)
  - "The Father", 1947; 513-27; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - The Feiled Meet Vaudeville Co., Un-dated; 903-14; 14 x 22 inches (Box C10)
  - "The Fortune Hunter", Un-dated; 513-70; 20 x 28 inches (Box D2)
    Larger copy in "D" size box
  - "The Fortune Hunter", Un-dated; 513-71; 21 x 29 inches (Box not specified)
  - "The Girl of the Golden West", Un-dated; 511-44; 11 x 17 inches (Box C5)
  - The Great system of Public Recreation since the Time of Rome, Un-dated; 392; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - The Great War and Woman's Part in It, Un-dated; 390; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - The Headless Horseman. Operetta by Douglas Moore, Stephen Vincent Benet. Stanford Memorial Hall May 22 [ca. 1940], 524-18; 22 x 14 inches (Box C5)
    1940 written on back (or possibly 1948).
  - "The Heart of Pierrot", 1921; 513-17; 11 x 14 inches (Box A3)
  - The History of Western Civilization Essay Prize for 1964-65, 2041; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A1)
    History, Dept. of
  - The History of Western Civilization Lectures Spring 1965, 2043; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A1)
    8.5 x 11 inches
  - The History of Western Civilization Lectures Winter 1965, 2042; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - "... The House of Bernarda Alba", 1951; 511-32; 14 x 20 inches (Box C6)
  - The Human Problems of South Vietman, 1969; 360; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - "The Hungover Games", 2015-021; 13 x 19 inches (Box B4)
    Mixed Company (Vocal group)
  - "The Importance of Being Earnest", 1926; 506-1; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - The Information Explosion: A Stanford Centennial Symposium, 1990 Oct 5-7; 2015-028; 16 x 22 inches (Box C11)
  - "The Inspector General", 1968; 5125; 11 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
  - "The Late George Apley", 1952; 511-36; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - "The Levite", 1941; 903-6; 22 x 28 inches (Box C10)
  - The libraries of Stanford celebrate the six-millionth acquisition: The Robert Creeley archive. Poetry reading by Robert Creeley with Robert Grenier and Leslile Scalapino. Oct. 21, 1993, 2006-059; 10 x 17 inches (Box B2)
    removed from 4digit
  - "The Madwoman of Chaillot", 1951; 511-31; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - The Magic Flute Opera by Mozart in English. Memorial Hall. March 7,8.9 [1946], 524-17; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - "The Maids", 1968; 5085; 11 x 17 inches (Box C6)
  - "The Maids", 1968; 513-72; 11 x 18 inches (Box B3)
  - The Making and Remaking of Mexico. Rethinking History, Culture, and Politics in the 20th Century; with keynote speakers Lorenzo Meyer and Carlos Monsivais. Nov. 13-15, 1997, 212-6; 21 x 12.75 inches (Box B1)
  - "The Man from Home", Un-dated; 5045; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - "The Marriage of Mr. Mississippi", 1961; 511-41; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - The Third Century--America as a Post-Industrial Society: Robert Nisbet, "The Future of the University", 1977 Jan 11
  - The Third Century--America as a Post-Industrial Society: Stanley Rothman, "The Mass Media in Post-Industrial Society, 1977 Jan 25; 2010-002
  - "The Master of Santiago", 1961; 511-40; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - The masters candidates in the Graduate Program in Documentary Film and Video present ...Based on a True Story, a screening of ten short doucmentaires. 10 June 2000., 2003-023; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - "The Merchant of Venice", 1951; 511-33; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - "The Midnight Mafia", Un-dated; 5104; 12 x 19 inches (Box C6)
  - The Ministry is the Medium, 1969; 364; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - "The Miser", 1948; 513-28; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - The New Civilization, Un-dated; 386; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - The New Soviet Union: Implications for the United States and Germany, 1991 May 1-2; 2015-002; 11 x 17 inches (Box A6)
  - The Orchid Observed. Five Centuries of Botanical Illustration. An exhibit of books... November 12, 1982 through January 11, 1983, 2003-034; 12.5 x 19.5 inches (Box C4)
    Copy 2 is framed [from ASUL collection]; possibly going to M. Keller in DO
  - The Panama Canal--A Persisting Problem, 1965; 2015; 14 x 22 inches (Box A1)
  - The People's Party, 1968; 905-50; 11 x 17 inches (Box A4)
  - "The Pirates of Penzance", Un-dated; 513-48; 20 x 28 inches (Box C7)
    Other smaller paper copy is in A4
  - "The Place of the Church in the Modern World", 1969; 5183; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - "The Possessed", Un-dated; 511-57; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - "The Possessed", Un-dated; 511-58; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - The Power of the Word, 1968; 2018; 17 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - "The Present & Foreseeable Future" [comic], undated; 2015-013; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A6)
  - The Present Crisis in the French Universities., 1969; 205-7; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - The Presidential and Endowed Lectures in the Humanities and Arts. Lynn Hunt "The Novel and the Origins of Human Rights" April 8, 2002. Stanford Humanities Center., 2007-003; 16.25 x 16.75 inches (Box C4)
  - "The Princess of Enone", 1905-; 513-12; 14 x 20 inches (Box not specified)
  - "The Princess of Leeland", 1901-; 513-2; 42 x 28 inches (Box C7)
  - "The Queen's Husband", Un-dated; 513-34; 14 x 20 inches (Box C7)
  - "The Question", Un-dated; 511-48; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - "The Rank Outsider", 1902-; 513-9; 40 x 28 inches (Box B3)
  - "The Rank Outsider", 1902-; 513-10; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
    Drama Student Productions Misc.
  - The Raymond F. West Memorial Lectures on Immoratlity, Human Conduct and Human Destiny, Undated; 383; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - "The Relapse", 1949; 511-20; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - "The Return of Peter Grimm", 1949; 511-21; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)